<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">S4Claw</string>
    <string name="accessibility_service_description">Screen4Claw Device Service - Provides accessibility control and screen capture functionality</string>

    <string name="permission_activity_title">Permission Settings</string>
    <string name="accessibility_permission_title">Accessibility Permission</string>
    <string name="accessibility_permission_desc">Used for UI control and automation operations</string>
    <string name="screen_capture_permission_title">Screen Capture Permission</string>
    <string name="screen_capture_permission_desc">Used for capturing screenshots</string>

    <string name="permission_status_granted">Granted</string>
    <string name="permission_status_not_granted">Not granted</string>
    <string name="permission_request">Request Permission</string>
    <string name="permission_open_settings">Open Settings</string>

    <string name="button_enable">Enable</string>
    <string name="button_disable">Disable</string>
    <string name="button_retry">Retry</string>
    <string name="button_close">Close</string>

    <string name="toast_permission_granted">Permission granted</string>
    <string name="toast_permission_denied">Permission denied</string>
    <string name="toast_accessibility_enabled">Accessibility service enabled</string>
    <string name="toast_accessibility_disabled">Accessibility service disabled</string>
    <string name="toast_screen_capture_granted">Screen capture permission granted</string>
    <string name="toast_screen_capture_denied">Screen capture permission denied</string>

    <string name="disclosure_accessibility_title">Accessibility Service Disclosure</string>
    <string name="disclosure_accessibility_message">ForClaw needs to use Android Accessibility Service (AccessibilityService) to implement the following core features:\n\n• Read screen content: Get UI elements of current interface so AI understands what is displayed\n• Automation: Execute tap, swipe, type and other operations based on your commands\n• Navigation: Perform back, home and other navigation operations\n\nThis app will not collect, store or share your personal data through accessibility service. All screen information is processed locally on device for executing your AI commands.\n\nTap \"Agree &amp; Continue\" to confirm you understand and authorize this app to use accessibility service.</string>
    <string name="disclosure_screen_capture_title">Screen Capture Disclosure</string>
    <string name="disclosure_screen_capture_message">ForClaw needs to use screen recording (MediaProjection) to implement the following core features:\n\n• Capture screen: Get current screenshot so AI understands what you are viewing\n• Analyze UI elements: Identify buttons, text and other elements on screen to assist automation\n\nScreenshots are processed locally on device and will not be uploaded or shared with third parties.\n\nTap \"Agree &amp; Continue\" to confirm you understand and authorize this app to use screen recording.</string>
    <string name="disclosure_storage_title">File Access Disclosure</string>
    <string name="disclosure_storage_message">ForClaw needs \"All Files Access\" permission to implement the following core features:\n\n• File management: AI reads, creates and edits files on device based on your commands\n• Configuration storage: Save app configuration, chat history and skill plugins\n• Screenshot saving: Save screenshots for AI analysis\n\nThis app only accesses files when you initiate commands and does not scan or upload your files in background.\n\nTap \"Agree &amp; Continue\" to confirm you understand and authorize this app to access device files.</string>
    <string name="disclosure_agree">Agree &amp; Continue</string>

    <string name="notification_channel_name">Service Status</string>
    <string name="notification_channel_desc">Shows service running status</string>
    <string name="notification_title">Screen4Claw Service Running</string>
    <string name="notification_content">Accessibility and screen capture services activated</string>
</resources>
